schwans.com 2019-12-10

# Schwan's

Last updated: November 1, 2018

* * *

## Privacy Policy

Schwan's Home Service, Inc. is concerned about privacy issues and want you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information as described in this Privacy Policy. Most of the information we collect is gathered during the initial registration process. This includes items such as name, address, telephone number or email address. Sharing information with Schwan's Home Service, Inc. is strictly voluntary. 

Visitors who choose to browse our site without registering remain completely anonymous. Most of the site is accessible to all visitors located in geographic areas where delivery of SCHWAN'S® products is available. Registration is required to establish accounts, make purchases, change personal information, etc. 

Visitors may occasionally be required to provide their email address or any other contact information (such as mailing address, residential phone number or cell phone number) to access portions of the site. By providing us with your contact information you understand and agree that we, our agents, or third parties carefully selected by us, may use this contact information to occasionally send you information or call you (whether manually or through an auto-dialing system) about products, menu planning, specials, promotions, etc. Visitors may also opt to provide their contact information to Schwan's Home Service, Inc. at various nonrequired times. By providing your contact information in an optional area, you consent to us or third parties carefully selected by us, occasionally sending you information or calling you about products, menu planning, specials, promotions, etc. If you prefer not to receive this kind of information from Schwan's Home Service, Inc., your request will be promptly honored. (Please note, however, that all customers who purchase online will receive an email confirmation after their order is placed in addition to updates regarding the status of their order.) 

Occasionally, Schwan's Home Service, Inc. uses external vendors to provide specific services which may enhance our site or create a better experience for our customers. Further, we may hire agencies to assist us in administering consumer promotions, fulfilling orders, analyzing site use and data, etc. We may provide these agents access to your personal information if it is needed in order for them to perform their services on behalf of Schwan's Home Service, Inc. However, these agents are prohibited from using or disclosing your personal information for any other purpose and are required to keep your information confidential. 

For example, we use an outside source to provide advertising for schwans.com. This company also supplies advertising for other sites. Occasionally, our ad provider may use information about your visit to schwans.com (and other sites) to measure the effectiveness of their ads. They may also use information to supply advertisements about goods and services that may be interesting to you. Please be aware that the advertising provider Schwan's Home Service, Inc. uses does not have access to your name, email address or telephone number. The privacy of this information is protected by Schwan's Home Service, Inc. 

Schwan’s Home Service, Inc. may provide your mailing address to carefully selected third parties if we believe they may have offers or information that may be of interest to you. In addition, we may share all user information and data including personal information to a successor business in the event of a sale, merger, corporate reorganization or similar transaction. 

Schwan's Home Service, Inc., or our authorized third party partner(s), may also collect general information (such as the type of browser you use, the files you request, and the domain name and country from which you request information) to help us make our site serve you better. User-specific data about which pages our customers access may also be gathered. Digital and online data collected by Schwan's Home Service, Inc. is used to create customized recommendations and to tailor content for our customers. This helps make your shopping experience more personalized and complete. 

Schwan's Home Service, Inc. uses an outside company to measure the effectiveness of our keyword marketing. This technology uses cookies to collect information about our customers' actions on schwans.com but does not capture any personally identifiable information such as your name, email address or telephone number. The privacy of this information is protected by Schwan's Home Service, Inc. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the opportunity to accept or decline it. 

## Security

Schwan's Home Service, Inc. makes security a top priority. Any personal data you provide to us is stored on a secure server. Only Schwan's Home Service, Inc. employees, or their qualified agents, with proper authorization can view this information. In addition, each customer is protected through a unique username and password.

## Cookies

Like most websites, schwans.com uses a technology called "cookies." Cookies are small amounts of data stored on a user's hard disk. This information lets us know if you have visited our site previously. We use cookies to deliver content that matches your interests. This technology also makes it possible to remember your username and password, so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit. Schwan's Home Service, Inc. uses cookies only to provide better service for its customers. Most Web browsers allow you to choose not to accept cookies. Browsers can also be configured to notify you when a cookie is sent. If you decide not to allow cookies to be stored on your hard drive, schwans.com will not be accessible to you.

## Children and Parents

Schwans.com is not directed toward children under the age of 13. Children under age 13 should not submit personal information to Schwan's Home Service, Inc. without explicit permission of a parent or legal guardian. Where appropriate, Schwan's Home Service, Inc. will instruct children not to submit personal information and will require a parent or guardian's consent for anyone under the age of 13. If your child has already submitted personal information and you would like to have it removed, Schwan's Home Service, Inc. will do whatever possible to comply with your request.

## Product Reviews and Shared Stories

When you use our Product Review function or our Share A Story function it is important that you remember comments and information you post are publicly available, so please exercise caution when deciding whether to disclose anything personal about yourself.

All entries, posts, comments and reviews become the property of Schwan's Home Service, Inc. By posting, commenting and reviewing a product, you acknowledge and understand that Schwan's Home Service, Inc. has the right, but not obligation, to use said items in whatever fashion they deem necessary in their marketing/advertising collateral and that you will not be compensated in any fashion.

## Partners

From time to time we may share customer information with carefully selected providers of goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive mailings from these providers, you can notify us at any time by contacting us by telephone, 1-888-724-9267; email: [contact us](https://www.schwans.com/secure/customer-service/contact-us); or by writing us at Schwan's Home Service, Inc., 115 West College Drive, Marshall, MN 56258. It may take up to eight weeks to remove your information from that which is shared with these providers. 

Notwithstanding any other provision, we may also engage a third party partner for the purpose of identifying users and delivering to them interest-based content and advertisements. We may share information about you with our partners such as your name, postal address, email, or other identifier and may do so in non-human readable form to ensure the security of your information. Our partners also may collect information directly from your device, such as your IP address, device ID, and information about your browser or operating system; may combine our personal and non-personal information about you with information from other; and may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. To opt-out of third party cookies, please go to <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>. To opt-out of the use of your mobile device ID for targeted advertising, please see <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices>. 

## California Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of California, in addition to the rights set forth above, you have the right to request information from us regarding the manner in which we share certain categories of personal information with carefully selected third parties for their direct marketing purposes. California law gives you the right to send us a request at a designated address to receive the following information: 

  1. the categories of information we disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year; 
  2. the names and addresses of the third parties that received that information; and 
  3. if the nature of the third party's business cannot be determined from their name, examples of the products or services marketed. 

We may provide this information in a standardized format that is not specific to you. The designated email address for these requests is [here](https://www.schwans.com/secure/customer-service/contact-us). 

Currently, our online Services do not recognize automated browser signals regarding "do not track" instructions. If we develop this capability in the future, we will describe how we do so in our Privacy Policy. 

## Miscellaneous

Schwans.com may contain links to other sites. We do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. Your use of third-party websites and resources is at your own risk.

It may be necessary, if required by law or if pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations, to release your personally identifiable information.

Schwan's Home Service, Inc. reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. We will promptly reflect any such modifications in these Web pages.

By using schwans.com, you consent to our use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. As we implement new technology and introduce new services, we will update our Privacy Policy, so we encourage you to review it often. Any changes will be posted on this or a similar page of this Website.

Please note that third parties may collect personal information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use our online Services or browse other websites. 

Email Marketing—If you would like to unsubscribe from our emails, please click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails, or update your email preferences in our preference center.
